hello everyone this is chambers would be
three four five here and I'm going to be
seen Sonic on the ground someday enjoy
boom there's something missing
something not quite right and I can feel
it calling to me every night a little
voice inside tells me someone is out
there and I must never give up searching
everywhere someday we are gonna be
together some night that would be so
much better someday we will build upon
no one can write some day no mother
clouds a ball some night united in a lot
of love someday let's do I can only an
worldwide will be together some night
some night we are going to beat you
gather some night life would be so much
better someday we will build upon no one
can break yeah somebody no more talk
about the box all night you know I below
someday this doing can only had one way
beat you get some day some day be
together someday all right if
you like that comment rate subscribe
glad you like my new video of
y'all next week